It all seemed so simple:
defeat the mad scientist and ride into the sunset.
But sometimes victory leaves you buried under the ruins.
I was lucky: someone saved me.
For a change I’m not the only mysterious stranger in town.
But weeks have passed,  and the metropolis of weird science
is still waiting for its own savior.
Outlaws and escaped monsters roam the streets.
The Resistance is too weak, so someone else decided
to take matters into his own hands.
General Harker, the military genius of the city, came back from his exile.
He gathered the rest of the disorganized army. His forces are
a chaotic mess of weird machines... so far.
But they are slowly clearing out the streets.
He might not have seen eye to eye with Fulmigati,
but he regards me and the Resistance as a threat to the city.
A coalition of monsters and troublemakers.
As a hunter I won’t tolerate others hunting me.
I’m ready to fight. I have an underground Lair, new soldiers…
and my new, mysterious ally.
I’m quite used to unlikely companions, but Prisoner Seven is the most unusual so far.
A former test subject of the mad scientists, master of the Ink…
he’s certainly helpful, but I don’t know what to make of him.
Now he can prove his worth.
Harker’s troops are on the move. They want to control the foundries
so he can build more warmachines.
We will stop them in the sizzling, clanking heart of Borgova.
Let the battle begin!