As famous last stands go, the battle for Viaduct Junction
was quite spectacular.
Sadly, it doesn’t change the fact that we are losing this war.
I even had to leave behind important allies.
General Harker is a worthy opponent.
He has salvaged the mad scientist’s toybox, found some real treasures
and used them wisely.
Now the Force Domes are keeping us away
from strategically important positions
and the unnatural soldiers are forcing us back to the Lair.
Harker is on his way to occupy the foundries.
The mysterious Prisoner Seven promised to find a way
to destroy the Domes.
Until then, we must remain in the Lair that the General
is so desperate to find
So we will have to keep him busy.