My name is Van Helsing,
and I’m a monster hunter.
You could call it a twist of fate that I came to Borgovia
to help the monsters who once ruled this land…
…although it took a while to reach my destination.
At least the detour gave me an opportunity to explore the wilderness.
At times I was really grateful that I had my companion, Lady Katarina at my side.
I wouldn’t want her to hear that, though. For a ghost she can be remarkably vain…
and murderous.
Borgovia is a fascinating land… at least from a hunter’s perspective.
Also this is the only place where
the Ink, the dark material
of creation, leaks through
the cracks of the world.
A long time ago my father defeated
Borgovia’s immortal vampire lords
and entrusted the land to
a group of genius scientists.
During our travels we slowly began to suspect that it must have been a mistake.
When we entered the dark city of
Borgova, it became evident that
the new age of enlightenment had
only brought chaos and mayhem.
I did what I had to do. I found my
father’s underground lair
and gathered the members of the Resistance,
the rebellious mortals and immortals fighting together.
And how we fought!
It was glorious.
We battled impossible creatures.
We repelled tides of inhuman invaders.
And I wouldn’t rest until I had defeated the last mad scientist, Professor Fulmigati.
He even had a proper Doomsday Automaton.
Honestly? It was a hunter’s dream come true.
But as it turns out, winning the grand battle
sometimes opens up a brand new adventure.