It all began with a call for help.
A letter from Borgovia, addressed to Van Helsing,
the great monster-slayer.
My father.
He doesn’t take cases any more, but I am a hunter too.
So I set off on the journey with Lady Katarina,
my remarkable companion.
I’m an expert on the supernatural and I seem to be drawn to it.
Occasionally events get out of control and then we have to leave in quite a hurry.
Sometimes it’s Katarina’s fault.
She can be quite reckless at times.
Still, she always helps me save the day.
And… she also happens to be a ghost.
My father rescued her from Borgovia
and she has been bound to serve our family ever since.
Katarina often complains about it,
but I think she really likes the thrill of the adventure.
She is a charming soul, but she also has a darker side.
Good.
It comes in helpful when I’m in danger.
Somewhere along the way we slowly learned to work together.
And finally, in the cold rain of Venice, we became a team.
The last leg of the journey was by sea.
Apart from the Kraken, the pirates and the storms it was mostly uneventful.
I had time to ponder my mission.
Once Borgovia was a dark place where monsters lived.
long ago my father defeated the immortal kings,
created a peace treaty and entrusted the land to some enlightened individuals.
What could have happened there?
What could be even more frightening than the reign of monsters?
The closer we drew to Borgovia, the more confusing the rumors became.
The land behind the Thunderhead Mountains was wrapped in mystery.
As our carriage approached the mountain pass, I had a sense of foreboding.
It didn’t really surprise me when I heard an explosion.
The adventure has just begun.