I came to Borgovia to free the land from the tyranny of mad science,
but the fall of Fulmigati was the spark that ignited the flames of the civil war.
So I led the Resistance against the military genius who tried to destroy us.
I faced an army of mechanical monsters and defeated General Harker
only to suffer betrayal from my mysterious ally, Prisoner Seven,
who tricked me and obtained the most powerful artifact in the land,
the hidden death of Koschei the Deathless.
Prisoner Seven disappeared into the depths of the otherworld,
but I will track him down.
It’s not only about revenge.
I’m a hunter,
he is my nemesis
and he has a plan.
The citizens are looking to me for guidance,
but I must find Prisoner Seven first.
It's a tough decision.
Chaos reigns in Borgova.
Warbands, gangs and bickering political factions
want to take power into their own hands.
What's more
the city is plagued by the sudden appearance of the Cult of Seven.
Led by a mechanical monster, the beastly Infiltrator,
they break into Fulmigati’s former laboratories  and seize precious equipment.
Evidently my nemesis is behind all this,
and it can only be the beginning of something worse.
This time I know which facility the Infiltrator will attack next.
A secret laboratory and a horde of monsters…
Just like old times.